{
    "id": "8b0a32df10bd48bba1102fbce9c75503",
    "title": "English vocabulary quiz",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "She always …………………. to her elder sister.",
            "description": "To defer is to give in to someone",
            "answers": [
                "defers",
                "deflects",
                "defaces"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "902727f7c656480e93f4c26fa05a2ad1"
        },
        {
            "question": "May I return this toaster if it is .....................…?",
            "description": "If something is defective, it is faulty.",
            "answers": [
                "deflective",
                "defective",
                "deferential"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b823ff9b2d9d4759b36f3f2ca3cdd2de"
        },
        {
            "question": "The policeman’s badge ...................... the bullet.",
            "description": "To deflect is to prevent something undesirable from being aimed at you. ",
            "answers": [
                "defaced",
                "deduced",
                "deflected"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "aadfb254e43f438d992fd16cb4fbe4b9"
        },
        {
            "question": "His treatment of the elderly people was affectionate and .....................",
            "description": "Deferential means respectful.",
            "answers": [
                "defiance",
                "deferential",
                "defunct"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "2f21856cff8f4800907c7f1a237876ed"
        },
        {
            "question": "She has a ..................... that makes walking difficult.",
            "description": "Deformity means a malformation.",
            "answers": [
                "defiance",
                "deformity",
                "deflection"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "47926b09387c45e89ae1289fa4950dfa"
        },
        {
            "question": "After all those expenses, we ended the year with a ......................",
            "description": "Deficit means an excess of money spent over money earned.",
            "answers": [
                "deficit",
                "decorum",
                "deference"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "bc7642aa3fcc42aa9191bbe07e7bc12f"
        },
        {
            "question": "The company has been ..................... since the war.",
            "description": "If something is defunct it is no longer functioning.",
            "answers": [
                "defunct",
                "deferential",
                "deflective"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1b1fd1d26bf74064a1f0fe72175e3d08"
        },
        {
            "question": "He ………………… the book by writing on it.",
            "description": "To deface is to spoil the appearance of something.",
            "answers": [
                "decorated",
                "defered",
                "defaced"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "9078604e2b7a4607bced789c1349ba29"
        },
        {
            "question": "The child showed ..................... by refusing to eat.",
            "description": "Defiance means open refusal to obey.",
            "answers": [
                "reluctance",
                "defiance",
                "decorum"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "23535c7e356b4c59a1e055154f9e81e4"
        },
        {
            "question": "From her conversation, I ...................... that she had a large family.",
            "description": "To deduce is to form an opinion or conclusion.",
            "answers": [
                "defered",
                "deflected",
                "deduced"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "a0ede26f32fd491bbda9c0e8de96469a"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………… it advisable to buy property now.",
            "description": "To deem is to consider something in a particular way.",
            "answers": [
                "deter",
                "deem",
                "denounce"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e647eba8a42f41f1a07bcaf2ac703ad5"
        },
        {
            "question": "Jennifer always acts with ......................",
            "description": "Decorum means polite and socially acceptable behavior.",
            "answers": [
                "defunct",
                "deferential",
                "decorum"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "abe9ccee164e4d5b9fc033c6dba46928"
        }
    ]
}